<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<TranscendenceModule>

	<Type unid="&chEnricoGaul;">
		<Properties>
		</Properties>

		<Language>
			<Code id="missionIntro">
				(block (
					;	Count the number of mission intros that we've already
					;	given to the player. 0 means that we've never shown an
					;	intro before.

					(introCount (count
						(filter (msnFind "* +property:character.missionGiver=&chEnricoGaul;;") theMission
							(msn@ theMission 'isIntroShown)
							)
						))
					)
					(switch
						(geq introCount 3)
							(typTranslate gType 'missionIntro.default gData)

						(typTranslate gType (cat 'missionIntro. (+ introCount 1)) gData)
						)
					)
			</Code>

			<!-- First Mission Intro -->

			<Code id="missionIntro.1">
				(list
					{	descID: 'textIntro.1.1		labelID: 'actionIntro.1.1	translateType: gType	}
					{	descID: 'textIntro.1.2		labelID: 'actionIntro.1.2	translateType: gType	}
					)
			</Code>
			<Text id="textIntro.1.1">

				A gray-haired man in wrinkled militia blues stands at a console.
				A captain's insignia sits on his shoulder and the name 'Gaul' is
				printed above his heart.

				"What are you gawking at, civie? Can't you see there's work to
				do?"

				He musters up an intimidating look, but a whiff of gin betrays
				him.

			</Text>
			<String id="actionIntro.1.1">"[W]hat kind of work?"</String>
			<Text id="textIntro.1.2">

				He shakes his head and scoffs.

				"The kind that pays to fuel that kack ship of yours! Assuming
				you survive long enough to collect, that is.

				"This is the militia, %boy%&mdash;not an ice cream shop. You do
				the job that needs doing."

			</Text>
			<String id="actionIntro.1.2">"[I]'m ready."</String>

			<!-- Second Mission Intro -->

			<Code id="missionIntro.2">
				(list
					{	descID: 'textIntro.2.1		labelID: 'actionIntro.2.1	translateType: gType	}
					{	descID: 'textIntro.2.2		labelID: 'actionIntro.2.2	translateType: gType	}
					)
			</Code>
			<Text id="textIntro.2.1">

				The gray-haired man is staring off into space. His face is red 
				and his eyes are puffy. He stands up and frowns when you enter.

				"Well, look who's back! Ready for another job? Is this a 
				convenient time for you?"
			
			</Text>
			<String id="actionIntro.2.1">"[I]'m ready to help, captain."</String>
			<Text id="textIntro.2.2">

				"Yeah, well don't be so eager. This aint some cushy corporate 
				gig where you push a button and let the bots do the kill.

				"We work for a living here, %boy%."
			
			</Text>
			<String id="actionIntro.2.2">"[D]o you have a mission for me or not?"</String>

			<!-- Third Mission Intro -->

			<Code id="missionIntro.3">
				(list
					{	descID: 'textIntro.3.1		labelID: 'actionIntro.3.1	translateType: gType	}
					{	descID: 'textIntro.3.2		labelID: 'actionIntro.3.2	translateType: gType	}
					)
			</Code>
			<Text id="textIntro.3.1">

				Captain Gaul sits at his console watching a message from a young
				woman. She's dressed in a neolinen suit and wears a trendy hair 
				style. Gaul snaps the message off when he sees you.

				"Back already? You must be desperate for some coin."

			</Text>
			<String id="actionIntro.3.1">"[I] just want to help, captain."</String>
			<Text id="textIntro.3.2">

				Gaul laughs.

				"You're just passing through, %boy%. Sooner or later you'll be
				done with us and off to the next system. You think you're a 
				hero? Heros stay and fight day after day, even when it's easier
				to run."

			</Text>
			<String id="actionIntro.3.2">"[J]ust give me a mission, please!"</String>

			<!-- Subsequent Mission Intros -->

			<Code id="missionIntro.default">
				(list
					{	descID: 'textIntro.default.1	labelID: 'actionIntro.default.1	translateType: gType	}
					)
			</Code>
			<Text id="textIntro.default.1">

				Captain Gaul walks up to you. He has a tight smile on his face.

				"What the hell are you doing here, %name%? Don't you have better
				things to do than catch pissant drug smugglers?"
			
			</Text>
			<String id="actionIntro.default.1">"[K]nock it off, I'm trying to help."</String>

			<!-- COMMONWEALTH VOLUNTEER 01 -->

			<Code id="volunteer01.briefing">
				(typTranslate gType (cat 'volunteer01.briefing. (min (@ gData 'missionNumber) 3)) gData)
			</Code>
			<Text id="volunteer01.briefing.1">
			
				The gray-haired man grunts as he looks down at a screen.

				"All right. There's a drug smuggler just came into the
				system with a load of tempus. Your mission is to intercept the 
				ship and destroy it. We don't want that kack on our station.

				"We'll pay %reward% if you succeed. Clear?"

			</Text>
			<Text id="volunteer01.briefing.2">
			
				Captain Gaul scoffs.

				"%Boy%, I got more missions than you can handle. Everyone except
				me is in the Black Market, judging by the amount of drugs 
				flooding into the system!

				"We tagged another smuggler ship just yesterday. Your mission is
				to intercept and destroy.

				"We'll pay %reward% if you succeed. Clear?"

			</Text>
			<Text id="volunteer01.briefing.3">
			
				Captain Gaul grunts as he looks down at a screen.

				"Guess what!? I got another smuggler for you to air out. 
				Shocking, isn't it? Why bother getting a job when you can just
				fast-foward your life on tempus?

				"We'll pay %reward% if you succeed. Clear?"

			</Text>
			<Text id="volunteer01.successDebrief">

				The gray-haired man leans back on his chair.

				"Good. A nice clean hit. We don't want their filth on our
				station.

				"We've deposited %reward% to your account."

			</Text>
			<Text id="volunteer01.failureDebrief">

				The gray-haired man shouts as you enter:

				"What the kack are you doing? We're all alone out here, and if 
				we don't clean up this filth no one is going to do it for us.

				"Next time act like you actually care!"

			</Text>

			<!-- COMMONWEALTH VOLUNTEER 02 -->

			<Code id="volunteer02.briefing">
				(typTranslate gType (cat 'volunteer02.briefing. (min (@ gData 'missionNumber) 3)) gData)
			</Code>
			<Text id="volunteer02.briefing.1">

				The gray-haired man stares at you then shakes his head.

				"All right, %boy%. I hope you can handle this.

				"There's %targetName% in the system, and the station council has
				grown a backbone and decided to act. I've been authorized to 
				deal with the threat, which means I'm authorizing you to blow
				it to hell.

				"We'll pay %reward% if you succeed. Clear?"

			</Text>
			<Text id="volunteer02.briefing.2">

				Captain Gaul chuckles.

				"Well it's your lucky day! The station council is cleaning up 
				the system. Must be an election coming up.

				"There's %targetName% in the system and I want you to go in and
				destroy it. Go ahead, make a mess if necessary.

				"We'll pay %reward% if you succeed. Clear?"

			</Text>
			<Text id="volunteer02.briefing.3">

				Captain Gaul scoffs.

				"All right, I forgot how much you hate banter.

				"Let me get to the point: We've got %targetName% in the system
				and I've been authorized to take it out. I want you to go out 
				there and destroy it.

				"We'll pay %reward% if you succeed. Clear?"

			</Text>
			<Text id="volunteer02.acceptReply.easy">

				"All right. I'll send the target to your computer. Don't worry
				about these guys&mdash;you can handle them. But don't get 
				careless either.

				"OK, get out of here."

			</Text>
			<Text id="volunteer02.acceptReply.normal">

				"All right. I'll send the target to your computer. Be careful,
				OK? These guys are not gonna make it easy for you.

				"OK, get out of here."

			</Text>
			<Text id="volunteer02.acceptReply.hard">

				Captain Gaul nods, then looks you in the eyes.

				"Listen, %name%, these guys are the real deal. They're 
				experienced, and they're well-armed. Go in strong and keep
				blasting until they're done.

				"But be careful. If your armor takes a beating, get out of 
				there. You're no good to me if you're dead.

				"OK, get out of here."

			</Text>
			<Text id="volunteer02.successDebrief">

				The gray-haired man leans back on his chair.

				"Good. A nice clean hit. That'll send a message.

				"We've deposited %reward% to your account."

			</Text>
			<Text id="volunteer02.textFailureDebrief">

				The gray-haired man shouts as you enter:

				"What the kack are you doing? We're all alone out here, and if 
				we don't stand up to these blowholes they're gonna own the whole
				system.

				"Next time act like you actually care!"

			</Text>

			<!-- COMMONWEALTH VOLUNTEER 03 -->

			<Code id="volunteer03.briefing">
				(typTranslate gType (cat 'volunteer03.briefing. (min (@ gData 'missionNumber) 3)) gData)
			</Code>
			<Text id="volunteer03.briefing.1">

				The gray-haired man stares at you then shakes his head.

				"A Commonwealth freighter sent out a distress call a few minutes
				ago. It sounds like they're under attack. I want you to go out
				there and help them out.

				"We'll pay %reward% if you can keep the freighter alive. Clear?"

			</Text>
			<Text id="volunteer03.briefing.2">

				Captain Gaul chuckles.

				"Be careful what you wish for, %boy%!

				"We've just picked up a distress call from a Commonwealth 
				freighter. It sounds like they're under attack and need 
				armed assistance.

				"We'll pay %reward% if you can save the freighter. Clear?"

			</Text>
			<Text id="volunteer03.briefing.3">

				Captain Gaul looks down.

				"All right, %name%, I've got a mission for you.

				"There's a Commonwealth freighter in trouble a couple of hundred
				light-seconds out. Looks like they're in the middle of a 
				firefight.

				"We'll pay %reward% if you can defend the freighter. Clear?"

			</Text>
		</Language>
	</Type>

</TranscendenceModule>
