<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<TranscendenceModule>

	<MissionType UNID="&msPsychEval01;"
			name=				"Psych Eval 01: Cure Xenopsychotic Disorder"
			attributes=			"commonwealth, commonwealthHospital"

			maxAppearing=		"1"
			priority=			"100"
			noDebrief=			"true"
			>

		<Properties>
			<Global id="nodeID"></Global>
			<Global id="stationID"></Global>
		</Properties>

		<Image imageID="&rsCommonwealthMedicalColony;" imageWidth="320" imageHeight="290"/>

		<Events>
			<!-- CREATE MISSION -->

			<OnGlobalUniverseCreated>

				;	Pick a Commonwealth hospital in the New Beyond to have this
				;	mission.

				(block (
					(stationList 
						(map (unvFindObject "t +unid:&stMedicalSuburb;;") 'excludeNil theEntry 
							(block (
								(objID (@ theEntry 0))
								(nodeID (@ theEntry 2))
								)
								(switch

									;	Must be in New Beyond (or SK)

									(and (!= nodeID 'SK)
											(not (sysHasAttribute nodeID 'newBeyond))
											)
										Nil

									;	Track ID and nodeID

									{
										nodeID: nodeID
										objID: objID
										}
									)
								)
							)
						)

					;	Pick a random station

					(stationEntry (random stationList))
					)

					;	Remember station picked
					;
					;	NOTE: It is OK if this list is Nil. In that case, the mission never
					;	shows up.

					(typSet@ gType 'stationID (@ stationEntry 'objID))
					(typSet@ gType 'nodeID (@ stationEntry 'nodeID))
					)
			</OnGlobalUniverseCreated>

			<CanCreate>

				;	Called from inside msnCreate and msnCanCreate.
				;	If defined, then return either true or nil to indicate that
				;	the mission can or cannot be created.
				;
				;	gData: Data passed in to msnCreate.
				;	aOwnerObj: Object that create the mission (or nil)

				(switch
					;	Only works for designated station

					(!= (objGetID aOwnerObj) (typ@ gType 'stationID))
						Nil

					True
					)

			</CanCreate>

			<OnCreate>
			</OnCreate>

			<!-- BRIEFING, ACCEPTING, DECLINING -->

			<OnAccepted>

				;	Called if the player accepts the mission.
				;
				;	gSource: Mission object.

				(block ()
					(msnSuccess gSource)
					)

			</OnAccepted>

			<OnDeclined>

				;	Called if the player rejects the mission. The mission is 
				;	already running (OnStarted has been called).
				;
				;	gSource is mission object.

			</OnDeclined>

		</Events>

		<Language>

			<!-- Code Points -->

			<Text id="Summary">
				(msnTranslate gSource 'textSummary {
					systemName: (sysGetName)
					})
			</Text>
			<Text id="Intro">
				(list
					{	descID: 'textIntro1		labelID: 'actionIntro1	}
					{	descID: 'textIntro2		}
					{	descID: 'textIntro3		labelID: 'actionIntro3	}
					{	descID: 'textIntro4		labelID: 'actionIntro4	}
					{	descID: 'textIntro5		labelID: 'actionIntro5	}
					{	descID: 'textIntro6		labelID: 'actionIntro6	}
					{	descID: 'textIntro7		labelID: 'actionIntro7	}
					{	descID: 'textIntro8		labelID: 'actionIntro8	}
					{	descID: 'textIntro9		labelID: 'actionIntro9	}
					{	descID: 'textIntro10	labelID: 'actionIntro10	}
					{	descID: 'textIntro11	labelID: 'actionIntro11	}
					{	descID: 'textIntro12	labelID: 'actionIntro12	}
					)
			</Text>
			<Text id="Briefing">
				(list
					{	descID: 'textBriefing1	acceptLabelID: 'actionAccept	declineLabelID: 'actionDecline	}
					)
			</Text>
			<Text id="AcceptReply">
				(list
					{	descID: 'textAcceptReply1 }
					)
			</Text>
			<Text id="DeclineReply">
				(list
					{	descID: 'textDeclineReply1 
						actions: (list
							{
								labelID: 'actionDecline1
								nextPage: 'confirmed
								}
							{
								labelID: 'actionDecline2
								nextPage: 'declined
								}
							)
						}
					{	id: 'confirmed
						descID: 'textDeclineConfirmed
						nextPage: 'forceUndock
						code: (lambda ()
							(plyDestroyed gPlayer (typTranslate &msPsychEval01; 'msgTreated))
							)
						}
					{	id: 'declined
						descID: 'textDeclineReply2
						}
					)
			</Text>

			<!-- Text -->

			<Text id="Name">
				Psych Evaluation
			</Text>
			<Text id="textSummary">

				You go to a hospital for a psych evaluation.

			</Text>
			<Text id="textIntro1">

				You wander the halls of the hospital and find yourself at the 
				psychiatric department. You feel light-headed and out-of-breath.
				You feel a strong urge to run away, but somehow you find the
				strength to go inside.

				A medtech sees you: "Can I help you?"

			</Text>
			<String id="actionIntro1">"[I]'m a pilgrim..."</String>
			<Text id="textIntro2">

				The medtech turns pale and freezes. She shouts, "Code violet!"

				She walks slowly towards you, hands open. "Everything's going to
				be OK. What's your name, pilgrim?"

				You hear people running behind you. You turn quickly but it's 
				too late. A hand grabs you and you feel a pinch in your neck.

				You black out before you hit the floor.
			
			</Text>
			<Text id="textIntro3">

				You wake up in a brightly lit exam room. A bald man in a blue 
				neolinen suit is sitting next to you. He looks up from his 
				infopad and smiles at you.
				
				You notice that you're strapped to a bed.

			</Text>
			<String id="actionIntro3">"[L]et me out of here!"</String>
			<Text id="textIntro4">

				The bald man rubs his chin.

				"Is that really what you want?

				"You came to us, remember? You came to us, I imagine, because
				deep down, you know you need help."

			</Text>
			<String id="actionIntro4">"[H]ow can you help me?"</String>
			<Text id="textIntro5">

				"We've been studying pilgrims for decades. Our center 
				specializes in treating pilgrims, and we've had some success
				lately.

				"We can cure you, if you want."
			
			</Text>
			<String id="actionIntro5">"[Y]ou can stop Domina's influence?"</String>
			<Text id="textIntro6">

				The bald man shakes his head.

				"Domina isn't real. She's a story&mdash;an explanation that you
				latched on to when your compulsion started.

				"Your compulsion to travel to the core is real. The changes to 
				your brain are real.

				"But Domina is not real. There's no one waiting for you at the 
				core."
			
			</Text>
			<String id="actionIntro6">"[B]ut Domina's powers..."</String>
			<Text id="textIntro7">

				"The powers are real, but they don't come from Domina!

				"The Ancient Races built a network of stargates, right? A 
				highway system for the galaxy using some unknown and near 
				magical technology. We've been using stargates for centuries.

				"I think they also built a communications network. A way to 
				communicate with each other and to command their powers."
			
			</Text>
			<String id="actionIntro7">"[A] communications network?"</String>
			<Text id="textIntro8">

				"Yes! Somehow&mdash;I don't know how&mdash;your brain is 
				connected to that network and can tap in to its powers. The
				Ancient Races probably used it to talk to each other 
				telepathically.

				"But human brains aren't compatible, and you've suffered brain 
				damage, which is causing the compulsion, the hallucinations, 
				everything."
			
			</Text>
			<String id="actionIntro8">"[B]rain damage?"</String>
			<Text id="textIntro9">

				"Yes! OK, now here's the hard part:

				"We can't treat you unless you consent. But your compulsion is
				going to resist treatment. That's why you're strapped down: we
				want to give you a chance to accept treatment voluntarily.

				"You're going to have to summon every last bit of mental energy
				and agree to let us treat you."
			
			</Text>
			<String id="actionIntro9">"[B]ut how can you be sure?"</String>
			<Text id="textIntro10">

				The bald man leans back and puts his hands together.

				"You're either suffering brain damage from an alien technology,
				or you've been chosen by an invisible, all-powerful goddess to 
				save humanity.

				"Which is more likely?"
			
			</Text>
			<String id="actionIntro10">"[C]an you scan for brain damage?"</String>
			<Text id="textIntro11">

				The bald man frowns.

				"It's not that easy. It's not an obvious mass or other gross 
				change. Your brain has been rewired. It looks completely normal.

				"But it's obviously not acting normal."
			
			</Text>
			<String id="actionIntro11">"[S]o you don't have proof."</String>
			<Text id="textIntro12">

				The bald man sighs.

				"Nothing can be proven! Maybe we're all inside a digital 
				simulation. Or maybe I'm just another hallucination for you.
				And I guess it's possible that Domina is real even though we 
				have no objective evidence of her.

				"But even if those are all possible, none of them are likely.
				The most likely explanation, by far, is that you have 
				xenopsychotic disorder, which we can treat.

				"But you have to trust me."
			
			</Text>
			<String id="actionIntro12">"[I] just need faith, right?"</String>
			<Text id="textBriefing1">

				The bald man shakes his head.

				"I've given you as much data as I can. If you're convinced that
				you're special and that you've been chosen by a higher power, by
				all means walk out of here.

				"But if you want to stop running and have a normal life again, I
				can help you.

				"Do you want a normal life again?"

			</Text>
			<String id="actionAccept">"[N]o! You're wrong, and I know what I'm doing."</String>
			<String id="actionDecline">"[Y]es, I want to give up my quest."</String>
			<Text id="textAcceptReply1">
				
				The bald man looks down.

				"Pilgrim life expectancy is not high. Space beyond the 
				Commonwealth is more violent than you can imagine. Slavers might
				capture you, or teratons could rip you open just for fun. Death
				in battle is probably your best outcome.

				"I'm truly sorry I couldn't help you."

			</Text>
			<Text id="textDeclineReply1">

				The bald man nods.

				"Good! I knew you could do it! Being willing to consider 
				treatment is a good sign; it means the brain damage is not too
				advanced. You have a good chance of recovery.

				"The treatment will not be easy. We'll put you into a coma and
				rewire your brain with electroconvulsive therapy. There are 
				risks, of course, but if successful, you'll eventually heal.

				"Do you want to start treatment?"

			</Text>
			<String id="actionDecline1">"[Y]es, I want the treatment."</String>
			<String id="actionDecline2">"[N]o, let me think it over."</String>
			<Text id="textDeclineReply2">

				The bald man looks skeptical.

				"OK, but don't take too long. Your compulsion will take over
				and keep you from getting the treatment you need."

			</Text>
			<Text id="textDeclineConfirmed">

				You feel no different at first. But as you probe your mind for
				the presence of Domina you feel a rising panic. What will you do
				without her? Without your mission? How can anything ever be the
				same?

				The bald man is moving in slow motion. He's yelling for 
				something. Two medtechs crash into the room wielding injectors
				and probes. One of them begins pounding your chest.

				You feel Domina inside you. She is sad, but not	surprised. You 
				hold on to her as long as you can, but then a wave of darkness 
				washes over you and you plunge into oblivion.

			</Text>
			<Text id="SuccessMsg"></Text>
			<Text id="FailureMsg"></Text>

			<Text id="msgTreated">

				accepted treatment for xenopsychotic disorder

			</Text>
		</Language>
	</MissionType>

</TranscendenceModule>
